[{"answer": "It's hard to tell.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "And from what you're hearing and feeling, has the tornado passed close to you?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Is that what you're hearing?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't think so much that people ignored the warning.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "What happened here?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "We are actually not (AUDIO GAP).", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Brandon, what can you see right now?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "We are now -- yes, sir, we are heading right towards Moore.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "So, Brandon, just to confirm, you are heading towards Moore, is that right?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I cannot confirm a tornado in Moore.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "This is a very powerful storm.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "And in terms of the strength and power of the storm that you're experiencing, how would you describe it?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I cannot confirm on any sort of cars being flipped or I can confirm factual damage because we are right on a previous tornado path of damage, so I can't -- I can't figure out if that is previous damage or if that was current damage.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What kind of thing are you picking up on?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "There was a confirmed tornado, it wasn't a particularly strong tornado.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What do we know about Moore itself in terms of whether a tornado has touched down?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "It is a very serious situation.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "What can you tell me?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, listen to the newscasters on the radio.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What should they be doing?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "At this time, we are trying to get the highways cleared off.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Governor, are you hearing reports of injuries fatalities at this stage?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, looking at a map right now, of the storm itself, it is lit up pretty good right over Moore.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Have you picked up any intelligence about what may be happening there?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "We have been dropping south away from the cell and they just keep reforming more tornadoes, more tornadoes back out to the west.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Are those tornado sirens going off?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "They are tornado sirens.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What are they?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "You have to watch where you are and for awhile, being in your car is still the safest place.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What do you think the best course of action is for anybody in a car on one of these interstates?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Can you hear me?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "We are about 10 miles south of Minco right now.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "What is going on where you are?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "We did see a very large three story house with the whole top roof gone or the whole top second floor and roof gone.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "In terms of damage that you've seen to vehicles or to property, what have you seen so far?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, since we can't really get on any of the main highways, I honestly don't know right this second.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Where will you be going to next?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "ANDOLPH: Absolutely chaos.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "What is the state of play where you are?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "The best thing for them to do is exit the interstate, whether it's I-40, I-240, I-35, exit the interstate and seek immediate shelter.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "What is the best thing they can do?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I don't -- I cannot confirm any numbers at this time.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "And in terms of people who may have been casualties, in terms of injuries or possibly even fatalities, what can you tell me?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "The best thing for them to do, especially -- the winds like I said will suck them out of their car.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "If people are literally jam-packed in what is being described as a parking lot on one of these interstates and they simply can't exit, what is the best thing they can do?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Have you in your time as a state trooper encountered anything quite like this?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, the way I understand it, I think you're correct, it's moved on past us.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Have you heard that?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, I think (INAUDIBLE) there is so much chatter going on, a lot of people responding to different things.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Can you tell me anything about that?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Not in El Reno.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Is that your view?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Right now, I don't have information on what we're seeing at the moment.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "What are you seeing coming in at the moment?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Are you anticipating having a lot of people in with a lot of injuries?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "We actually saw that.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "What are you hearing?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I don't have a report back on that yet.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "And, Mr. Mayor, in terms of damage to property or injuries to people in Moore, what can you tell me?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Not so much in Moore.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Is it your understanding that people may have been injured in Moore?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes, sir, that's what we're hearing.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "And from other local reports that you're seeing, are they matching what the state trooper told me, that there have just been an extraordinary large number of crashes involving vehicles?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "It's extremely bad due to the time of day that it impacted the metro.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "From what you're seeing and hearing, how bad is this on the ground?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I haven't seen any reports but we've been tracking the storms throughout the day and we just in our vehicle probably checked at least three overturned vehicles on their tops and probably saw another three or four that were left just abandoned in roadway.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Have you seen any local reports about the number of car accidents and crashes that have been happening tonight?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Well, it started off as just a single what we call super cell west of El Reno and it intensified into several super cells.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Ben, in terms of the power and strength of this storm, how would you describe it to me?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "We're probably going to continue to head south until it's kind of a state of emergency in the metro area right now.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "And where will you be headed now, Ben?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Yes, you bring up a good point.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "What do you know about that?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Loud and clear.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Mr. Lamb, can you hear me?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Piers, it's early for assessment, I know you talked to highway patrol.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What can you tell me, sir?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "AMB: Well, it's not easy.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "And as lieutenant governor of the state, how do you feel about the fact this is coming so soon after the devastation in Moore?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I don't want to speculate.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "From what you're seeing and hearing, do you imagine there are many more casualties?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Yes, most definitely.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Is the particular problem, do you think, what is happening on the interstates tonight?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Well, the most important thing is not to find yourself stuck in the water.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "What advice do you give people who may be stuck in their car on one of these interstates?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it does extend all the way on up toward St. Louis.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "How widespread is it now, do we believe?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "Yes, that's what I think.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "The line is funneling out of the area.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Nick, what's going on there now?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "The house that we saw, it was definitely damaged.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "And in terms, again, of damage that you're seeing or hearing about, how would you describe it?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "It definitely seems to be, looking at radar, there's nothing behind this building.", "docId": "130531pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "Do you believe the worst has passed through El Reno now, in that area?", "qSentId": 761}]